

# AIT AKKA N'ALLA ABDESSAMAD

WEB DEVELOPER

# **ABOUT ME**

A Graphic Designer with six years of experience working as the lead designer of Studio Shodwe and overseeing the individual project for brand development. Expert in video and layout creation, which is proved to be a valuable addition to developing the company's design project. Always use the out-of-the-box principle in creating the project, so it will come out with more powerful exposure and strength to attract public attention to the promotion campaign. Hard worker and have experience in leading a team of designers, and I can't wait to implement my skill and experience in your company.

# **EXPERIENCE**

### Freelance Graphic Designer

2014 - 2016

 Created the festival banner for the local food festival in June 2015, which has successfully attracted more than 2000 people from other cities.

## **Professional Graphic Designer**

Studio Shodwe ( 2017 - 2022 )

 Created the festival banner for the local food festival in June 2015, which has successfully attracted more than 2000 people from other cities.



# **EDUCATION**

**Bachelor of Arts in Communication Visual Design** *Connor Hamilton University*2010 - 2014 | GPA: 3.85